Guide to the John Farquhar Fulton Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General Files, 1910-1960; Series I
  - Morgan, Constance Morrow, 1938 (Box 125, Folder 1727)
  - Morison, Robert, 1949-1959 (Box 125, Folder 1728)
  - Morison, S. E., 1928-1957 (Box 126, Folder 1729)
  - Morris, Daniel, 1931-1932 (Box 126, Folder 1730)
  - Morrow, Rufus, 1939-1940 (Box 126, Folder 1731)
  - Morse, H. Marston, 1943-1945 (Box 126, Folder 1732)
    See also: Series II, Box 247, Folders 787-791
  - Moruzzi, Giuseppe, 1938-1960 (Box 126, Folder 1733)
  - Mosby Co., 1930-1936 (Box 126, Folder 1734)
  - Motlet, Norman, 1949, 1951 (Box 126, Folder 1735)
  - Motokawa, Koiti, 1948-1956 (Box 126, Folder 1736)
  - Mourgue, Raoul, 1931-1946 (Box 126, Folder 1737)
  - Muirhead, Arnold
    - 1922-1928 (Box 126, Folder 1738-1740)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 127, Folder 1741-1746)
    - 1934-1939 (Box 128, Folder 1747-1752)
    - 1940-1956 (Box 129, Folder 1753-1760)
    - 1957-1960, undated (Box 130, Folder 1761)
  - Multhauf, Robert, 1953-1956 (Box 130, Folder 1762)
  - Munly, W. C., 1941-1942 (Box 130, Folder 1763)
  - Muralt, Alex Von, 1948-1954 (Box 130, Folder 1764)
  - Murphy, James Peter, 1936-1960 (Box 130, Folder 1765)
  - Na (Box 130, Folder 1766)
  - Ne (Box 130, Folder 1767)
  - Ng-Ny (Box 130, Folder 1768)
  - Nachmansohn, David
    See also: box 135, folder 1839
    See also: box 223, folder 425
    - 1937-1939 (Box 130, Folder 1769)
    - 1940-1960 (Box 131, Folder 1770-1772)
  - Nahum, Louis, 1935-1960 (Box 131, Folder 1773)
  - Nathan Smith Club, 1952-1960 (Box 131, Folder 1774)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1931-1957 (Box 131, Folder 1775)
  - National Cyclopedia of American Biography, 1932-1947 (Box 131, Folder 1776)
  - National Hospitals for Nervous Diseases [centenary celebrations], 1960 (Box 131, Folder 1777)
  - National Institute of Health. ad hoc committee on history of medicine, 1958-1960 (Box 131, Folder 1778-1779)
  - National Paraplegia Foundation, 1948-1958 (Box 132, Folder 1780)
  - National Physicians Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 132, Folder 1781)
  - National Research Council
    See: box 231-247, folders 532-791
  - National Research Council of Canada, 1941-1944 (Box 132, Folder 1782)
  - National Science Foundation, 1954-1957 (Box 132, Folder 1783)
  - National War History Commission, 1942 (Box 132, Folder 1784)
  - Naval Medical Research Institute, 1944-1945 (Box 132, Folder 1785)
  - Naylor, Mildred V., 1943-1951 (Box 132, Folder 1786)
  - Negrin, Juan, 1955-1959 (Box 132, Folder 1787)
  - Neuburger, Max, 1925-1950 (Box 132, Folder 1788)
  - New England Journal of Medicine, 1934-1958 (Box 132, Folder 1789)
  - New England Post-graduate Assembly, 1941 (Box 132, Folder 1790)
  - New York Academy of Medicine
    - 1928-1951 (Box 132, Folder 1791)
    - 1952-1958 (Box 133, Folder 1792-1793)
  - New York Neurological Society, 1931-1958 (Box 133, Folder 1794)
  - New York Society for Medical History, 1942 (Box 133, Folder 1795)
  - New York Zoological Society, 1938-1959 (Box 133, Folder 1796)
  - Newberger, Frederick, 1939 (Box 133, Folder 1797)
  - Newburgh, Lewis, 1942-1945 (Box 133, Folder 1798)
  - Newell, R., 1942-1944 (Box 133, Folder 1799)
  - Newton, William H., 1938-1942 (Box 133, Folder 1800)
  - Ngowyang, G., 1933-1947 (Box 133, Folder 1801)
  - Nicholas, John S., 1933-1952 (Box 133, Folder 1802)
  - Nicolesco, Jean and Stephen, 1932-1960 (Box 133, Folder 1803)
  - Nicoll, Allardyce, 1937 (Box 133, Folder 1804)
  - Nicolson, Marjorie, 1933-1950 (Box 133, Folder 1805)
  - Niedert, George, 1944-1956 (Box 133, Folder 1806)
  - Nielson, Aage, 1936-1946 (Box 133, Folder 1807)
  - Nims, Leslie, 1939-1959 (Box 133, Folder 1808-1809)
    See also: box 223, folder 426
  - Niven, Janet, 1947-1960 (Box 133, Folder 1810)
  - Nobel Foundation, 1953-1955 (Box 133, Folder 1811)
  - Norman, Dr. Hubert J., 1931-1944 (Box 133, Folder 1812)
  - Norton and Co.
    See: box 176, folders 2616-2617
  - Novarr, David, 1940-1960 (Box 134, Folder 1813)
  - Nowinski, Wiktor W., 1951-1955 (Box 134, Folder 1814)
  - Noyes, C. Reinold, 1930-1959 (Box 134, Folder 1815)
  - Nu Sigma Nu Fraternity, 1951-1956 (Box 134, Folder 1816)
  - Nuffield, William Richard Morris and Lillian, 1940-1942 (Box 134, Folder 1817)
  - Nulson, Frank, 1947-1956 (Box 134, Folder 1818)
  - Nyboer, Jan, 1944-1959 (Box 134, Folder 1819)
  - O-On (Box 134, Folder 1820)
  - Op-Oz (Box 134, Folder 1821)
  - Obrado, S. Alcalde, 1936-1954 (Box 134, Folder 1822)
  - Ohio Academy of Science, 1939-1940 (Box 134, Folder 1823)
  - Old Sturbridge Village, 1953-1960 (Box 134, Folder 1824)
  - Oldberg, Eric, 1930-1949 (Box 134, Folder 1825)
  - O'Leary, James, 1930-1958 (Box 134, Folder 1826)
  - Olivecrona, H., 1932-1955 (Box 134, Folder 1827)
  - Oliver, John Rathbone, 1932-1933 (Box 134, Folder 1828)
  - Oliver, Peter, 1937-1938 (Box 134, Folder 1829)
  - Oljenick, Ignaz, 1930-1940 (Box 135, Folder 1830)
  - Olmstead, James Montrose Duncan, 1924-1956 (Box 135, Folder 1831)
  - Olmsted, Frederick, 1944 (Box 135, Folder 1832)
  - O'Malley, Charles Donald, 1943-1960 (Box 135, Folder 1833-1835)
  - Omega Club, College of Physicians and Surgeons, 1942 (Box 135, Folder 1836)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1947-1960 (Box 135, Folder 1837)
    See also: box 89, folders 1233-1238
  - Oppenheimer, Jane, 1942-1959 (Box 135, Folder 1838)
  - Ordway, Samuel, 1920-1960 (Box 135, Folder 1839)
  - Orr, H. Winnett, 1944-1956 (Box 136, Folder 1840)
  - Osborn, James M., 1944-1958 (Box 136, Folder 1841)
  - Osgood, Robert, 1926-1928 (Box 136, Folder 1842)
  - Osler, Grace
  - Osler Club, 1928-1960 (Box 136, Folder 1843-1844)
  - Osler Library, 1950-1958 (Box 136, Folder 1845)
    See also: boxes 54-55, folders 793-811
  - Osler Society, McGill University, 1944 (Box 136, Folder 1846)
  - Osler Society, Oxford University, 1923-1957 (Box 136, Folder 1847)
  - Osterhout, Winthrop J. V., 1929-1951 (Box 136, Folder 1848)
  - Ott, Lawrence, 1931-1956 (Box 136, Folder 1849)
  - Oughterson, Ashley W., 1933-1958 (Box 136, Folder 1850)
  - Overholser, Winfred, 1943-1959 (Box 136, Folder 1851)
  - Owen, Philip, 1943-1946 (Box 136, Folder 1852)
  - Oxford Architectural and Historical Society, 1939, 1952 (Box 136, Folder 1853)
  - Oxford Post Office [England], 1928-1930 (Box 136, Folder 1854)
  - Oxford Society, 1934-1941, 1944-1951, 1959-1960 (Box 136, Folder 1855)
  - Oxford University, 1923-1941 (Box 136, Folder 1856-1857)
    See also: box 117, folder 1596
  - Oxford University Press
    See also: box 92, folders 1277-1278
    - 1926-1946 (Box 137, Folder 1858-1868)
    - 1947-1960 (Box 138, Folder 1869-1877)
  - Ozorio de Almeida, Miguel, 1930, 1940-1948 (Box 138, Folder 1878)
  - Pa (Box 139, Folder 1879)
  - Pe (Box 139, Folder 1880)
  - Pf-Pl (Box 139, Folder 1881)
  - Po-Pu (Box 139, Folder 1882)
  - Page, Irvine, 1935-1947 (Box 139, Folder 1883)
  - Pagel, Walter, 1944-1960 (Box 139, Folder 1884)
  - Palmer, Allen, 1939-1955 (Box 139, Folder 1885)
  - Palthe, P. M. van Wulfflen, 1940, 1947, 1952-1958 (Box 139, Folder 1886)
  - Pan American Medical Association, 1959-1960 (Box 140, Folder 1887)
  - Pan-Pacific Surgical Association, 1947-1948 (Box 140, Folder 1888)
  - Papez, James W, 1931-1940 (Box 140, Folder 1889)
  - Paradise, N. Burton, 1931-1935 (Box 140, Folder 1890)
  - Pardo, Leopoldo, 1938-1939 (Box 140, Folder 1891)
  - Parhad, Malcolm, 1946-1960 (Box 140, Folder 1892)
  - Pasqual, Wenceslao, 1938-1947 (Box 140, Folder 1893)
  - Passano Foundation, 1944-1954 (Box 140, Folder 1894)
  - Paterson, T. S., 1931-1939 (Box 140, Folder 1895)
  - Patton, Harry, 1946-1957 (Box 140, Folder 1896)
    See also: box 223, folder 427
  - Paul, John R., 1930-1960 (Box 140, Folder 1897)
  - Paul B. Hoeber Inc., 1926-1943 (Box 140, Folder 1898-1900)
  - Paulian, D., 1932-1939 (Box 140, Folder 1901)
  - Paulson, Moses, 1958-1959 (Box 140, Folder 1902)
  - Payne, Leonard, 1953-1959 (Box 140, Folder 1903)
  - Peabody, Anne, 1937-1942 (Box 140, Folder 1904)
  - Pearl, Raymond, 1933 (Box 140, Folder 1905)
  - Pearson, Norman, 1932-1959 (Box 140, Folder 1906)
  - Pederson, Bethsabe, 1951-1958 (Box 140, Folder 1907)
  - Peerenboom, Cyril, 1940-1958 (Box 141, Folder 1908)
    See also: box 68, folders 945-951
  - Pekárek, Zdenek Josef, 1946-1948 (Box 141, Folder 1909)
  - Pellegrini, Francesco, 1948-1959 (Box 141, Folder 1910)
  - Penfield, Wilder, 1927-1959 (Box 141, Folder 1911-1913)
  - Pennington, L. A., 1940-1942 (Box 141, Folder 1914)
  - Perkins, Henrietta, 1939-1960 (Box 141, Folder 1915)
    See also: box 134, Folder 1829
  - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital, 1928-1938, 1948-1957 (Box 141, Folder 1916)
  - Peters, Charlotte, 1933-1951 (Box 141, Folder 1917)
  - Peters, John H, 1941, 1956-1958 (Box 141, Folder 1918)
  - Peterson, Robert, 1944-1951 (Box 141, Folder 1919)
  - Philadelphia Neurological Society, 1940-1941 (Box 141, Folder 1920)
  - Philadelphia Psychiatric Society, 1947 (Box 141, Folder 1921)
  - Phillips, Robert, 1932-1938 (Box 141, Folder 1922)
  - Phillips, Stephen, 1932, 1959 (Box 141, Folder 1923)
  - Physiological Abstracts, 1928-1938 (Box 141, Folder 1924)
  - Physiological Reviews, 1932-1937, 1946 (Box 141, Folder 1925)
  - Physiological Society, 1926-1954 (Box 141, Folder 1926)
  - Physiological Zoology, 1928-1931 (Box 141, Folder 1927)
  - Pi-Suñer, August, 1927-1951 (Box 142, Folder 1928)
  - Pi-Suñer, Jaime, 1927-1960 (Box 142, Folder 1929-1930)
  - Pickard, Madge, 1945-1946 (Box 142, Folder 1931)
  - Pickering, George, 1927-1960 (Box 142, Folder 1932)
  - Pickering, John, 1938 (Box 142, Folder 1933)
  - Pickett, Judy, 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 142, Folder 1934)
  - Pierce, Harold F., 1930-1953 (Box 142, Folder 1935)
  - Pierson, George, 1958-1960 (Box 142, Folder 1936)
  - Pijoan, Michel, 1931-1945 (Box 142, Folder 1937-1938)
  - Pike, Frank, 1931-1932 (Box 142, Folder 1939)
  - Pilcher, Cobb, 1934-1949 (Box 142, Folder 1940)
  - Pinkston, James, 1934-1938 (Box 142, Folder 1941)
  - Pitfield, Robert, 1930 (Box 143, Folder 1942)
  - Pitts, Robert, 1940-1952, 1959 (Box 143, Folder 1943)
    See also: box 223, folder 428
  - Placzek, Siegfried, 1943-1946 (Box 143, Folder 1944)
  - Platt, Robert, 1949-1958 (Box 143, Folder 1945)
  - Pliefke, Frida, 1940-1953 (Box 143, Folder 1946)
  - Plimpton Press, 1938 (Box 143, Folder 1947)
  - Poling, James, 1940-1942 (Box 143, Folder 1948)
  - Poljak, Stephen, 1932-1955 (Box 143, Folder 1949-1950)
  - Pollock, Lewis, 1937-1948 (Box 143, Folder 1951)
  - Pool, I. Lawrence, 1948-1959 (Box 143, Folder 1952)
  - Poppen, John, 1940-1943 (Box 143, Folder 1953)
  - Porter, Eugene L., 1926-1927, 1940-1949 (Box 143, Folder 1954)
  - Porteus, Stanley, 1954 (Box 143, Folder 1955)
  - Post, Helen, 1942-1955 (Box 143, Folder 1956)
  - Powell, Lawrence, 1953-1955 (Box 143, Folder 1957)
  - Power, D'Arcy, 1925-1940 (Box 143, Folder 1958)
  - Poynter, F. Noel L., 1952-1960 (Box 143, Folder 1959)
  - Pratt, Frederick, 1928-1940, 1958 (Box 143, Folder 1960)
  - Prendergast, J., 1930-1931 (Box 144, Folder 1961)
  - Pribram, Karl, 1948-1959 (Box 144, Folder 1962)
  - Price, Derek John, 1959 (Box 144, Folder 1963)
  - Price, Lucien, 1939-1957 (Box 144, Folder 1964)
  - Priestly, J. G., 1930-1933 (Box 144, Folder 1965)
  - Princeton University Press, 1946 (Box 144, Folder 1966)
  - Propper-Grachenkov, N., 1936-1965 (Box 144, Folder 1967)
  - Proskauer, Curt, 1950-1958 (Box 144, Folder 1968)
  - Prowell, Jane, 1948-1949 (Box 144, Folder 1969)
  - Psychosomatic Medicine, 1938-1940 (Box 144, Folder 1970)
  - Putnam, Tracy J, 1932-1947 (Box 144, Folder 1971)
  - Putti, Vittorio, 1930-1937 (Box 144, Folder 1972)
  - Q, 1973 (Box 144, Folder 1973)
  - Quarterly Journal of ExperimentalPhysiology, 1928-1950 (Box 144, Folder 1974)
  - Quastel, J. Hirsch, 1940-1946 (Box 144, Folder 1975)
  - Quen, Jacques, 1953-1959 (Box 144, Folder 1976)
  - Ra (Box 144, Folder 1977)
  - Re (Box 145, Folder 1978)
  - Rh-Ri (Box 145, Folder 1979)
  - Ro-Rop (Box 145, Folder 1980)
  - Ros-Ry (Box 145, Folder 1981)
  - Radbill, Samuel X., 1936-1959 (Box 145, Folder 1982)
  - Raddin, Joseph B., 1958-1960 (Box 145, Folder 1983)
  - Rademaker, G. G. J., 1925-1934 (Box 145, Folder 1984)
  - Rakieten, Nathan, 1931-1946 (Box 145, Folder 1985)
  - Ramon y Cajal Centenary, 1952-1953 (Box 146, Folder 1986)
  - Ramsey County Medical Society, 1934-1947 (Box 146, Folder 1987)
  - Ranson, S. Walter, 1926-1942 (Box 146, Folder 1988)
  - Rappleye, Willard C., 1930-1937 (Box 146, Folder 1989)
  - Rasmussen, Andrew T., 1932-1953 (Box 146, Folder 1990)
  - Rasponi, Caroline, 1942-1947 (Box 146, Folder 1991)
  - Ratcliffe, Herbert L., 1931 (Box 146, Folder 1992)
  - Ravdin, Isidor S., 1938-1951 (Box 146, Folder 1993)
  - Ravitz, Leonard J., 1953-1957 (Box 146, Folder 1994)
  - Rawson, Arthur J., 1941-1943 (Box 146, Folder 1995)
  - Rea, George, 1938-1949 (Box 146, Folder 1996)
  - Reddy, D. V. Subba, 1941-1960 (Box 146, Folder 1997)
  - Redlich, Frederick C., 1948-1955 (Box 146, Folder 1998)
  - Reed, Carlos I., 1944-1959 (Box 146, Folder 1999)
  - Reichner, Herbert
    - 1940-1953 (Box 146, Folder 2000)
    - 1954-1960 (Box 147, Folder 2001)
  - Reid, Edith C., 1931 (Box 147, Folder 2002)
  - Relf, Louise Fulton, 1915-1922 (Box 147, Folder 2003)
  - Relf, Louise Fulton and Richard, 1923-1960 (Box 147, Folder 2004-2007)
  - Renaissance Society of America, 1954-1960 (Box 147, Folder 2008)
  - Rey, André, 1937-1950 (Box 147, Folder 2009)
  - Rezende, Nilson, 1942-1959 (Box 147, Folder 2010)
  - Rheinberger, Margaret, 1933-1949 (Box 148, Folder 2011)
  - Rhinelander, F. W., 1930, 1957 (Box 148, Folder 2012)
  - Rhoads, Cornelius P., 1932-1947 (Box 148, Folder 2013)
  - Rhode Island Medical Society, 1932 (Box 148, Folder 2014)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Trust
    See also: box 319, folder 1
    - 1926-1936 (Box 148, Folder 2015-2021)
    - 1937-1959 (Box 149, Folder 2022-2024)
  - Richards, Alfred N., 1933-1958 (Box 149, Folder 2025)
    See also: box 170, folder 2442
  - Richards, Oscar W., 1931-1935 (Box 149, Folder 2026)
  - Richter, Curt P., 1927-1941 1951-1958 (Box 149, Folder 2027)
  - Riggs, Douglas, 1939-1953 (Box 149, Folder 2028)
  - Riley, Henry Alsop, 1933-1953 (Box 149, Folder 2029)
  - Riley, John J., 1947-1960 (Box 149, Folder 2030)
  - Rioch, David, 1929-1958 (Box 149, Folder 2031-2032)
  - Robb-Smith, Alastair, 1929-1955 (Box 149, Folder 2033)
  - Robinson, Franklin, 1950-1951 (Box 149, Folder 2034)
  - Robinson, John, 1923-1929 (Box 149, Folder 2035)
  - Rockefeller Foundation
    - 1927-1937 (Box 149, Folder 2036-2037)
    - 1938-1956 (Box 150, Folder 2038-2040)
  - Roddis, Lewis H., 1933-1959 (Box 150, Folder 2041)
  - Rogers, Frank B., 1953-1959 (Box 150, Folder 2042)
  - Rogers, H. S., 1922-1923 (Box 150, Folder 2043)
  - Rolleston, Humphrey, 1928-1944 (Box 150, Folder 2044)
  - Rolleston, J. D., 1933-1943 (Box 150, Folder 2045)
  - Rollins, Carl P., 1932-1959 (Box 150, Folder 2046)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin and Eleanor, 1940-1957 (Box 150, Folder 2047)
  - Roper, Eleanor, 1942-1948 (Box 150, Folder 2048)
  - Rose, John K., 1954-1960 (Box 150, Folder 2049)
  - Roseman, Ephraim, 1939-1941 (Box 150, Folder 2050)
  - Rosen, George, 1949-1960 (Box 150, Folder 2051)
  - Rosenbach Foundation, 1953-1954 (Box 150, Folder 2052)
  - Rosenblueth, Arturo, 1932-1939 (Box 150, Folder 2053)
  - Rosencrantz, Esther
    - 1940-1948 (Box 150, Folder 2054-2055)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 151, Folder 2056)
  - Rosenthal, Robert, 1932-1955 (Box 151, Folder 2057)
  - Rosenthal, Theodore, 1937-1953 (Box 151, Folder 2058)
  - Rosenwald, Lessing J., 1953-1959 (Box 151, Folder 2059)
  - Rosvold, Haldor, 1948-1959 (Box 151, Folder 2060)
  - Roth, Grace, 1940-1945 (Box 151, Folder 2061)
  - Rothschuh, K. E., 1950-1955 (Box 151, Folder 2062)
  - Roughton, F. J. W., 1923-1957 (Box 151, Folder 2063)
  - Roux, Lucien, 1938-1939 (Box 151, Folder 2064)
  - Rowntree, Leonard G., 1927-1933 (Box 151, Folder 2065)
  - Roxbury Clinical Records Club, 1943-1944 (Box 151, Folder 2066)
  - Royal Air Force, 1941-1944 (Box 151, Folder 2067)
  - Royal Society
    - General, 1924-1929, 1936, 1959-1960 (Box 151, Folder 2068)
    - Tercentenary celebrations, 1960 (Box 151, Folder 2069)
  - Royal Society of Medicine, 1928-1942, 1950-1959 (Box 151, Folder 2070)
  - Royal Swedish Academy of Sciences [bicentennial], 1939 (Box 151, Folder 2071)
  - Royle, Norman D., 1927-1932 (Box 151, Folder 2072)
  - Rubin, Morton, 1939-1945 (Box 152, Folder 2073)
  - Rubinstein, H. S., 1933-1939 (Box 152, Folder 2074)
  - Ruch, Theodore C., 1930-1960 (Box 152, Folder 2075-2079)
    See also: box 223, folders 430-431
  - Ruiz Moreno, Anibal, 1950-1960 (Box 152, Folder 2080)
  - Rule, Susan, 1928 (Box 152, Folder 2081)
  - Rush, Homer P., 1932-1954 (Box 152, Folder 2082)
  - Rushton, William A. H., 1930-1959 (Box 152, Folder 2083)
  - Russell, Diarmuid, 1940 (Box 152, Folder 2084)
  - Russell, Dorothy, 1930-1954 (Box 152, Folder 2085)
  - Russell, W. Ritchie, 1932-1959 (Box 152, Folder 2086)
  - Rylander, Gösta, 1948-1957 (Box 152, Folder 2087)
  - Sa (Box 153, Folder 2088)
  - Sca-Sch (Box 153, Folder 2089)
  - Sci-Sey (Box 153, Folder 2090)
  - Sh-Si (Box 153, Folder 2091)
  - Sj-Sn (Box 153, Folder 2092)
  - So (Box 154, Folder 2093)
  - Sp-Sq (Box 154, Folder 2094)
  - Sta-Sti (Box 154, Folder 2095)
  - Sto-Stu (Box 154, Folder 2096)
  - Su-Sz (Box 154, Folder 2097)
  - Sachs, Ernest, 1933-1958 (Box 154, Folder 2098)
  - Sachs, Ernest Jr., 1947-1959 (Box 155, Folder 2099)
  - Sa' di, Lufti M., 1934-1959 (Box 155, Folder 2100)
  - Sager, O., 1936-1960 (Box 155, Folder 2101)
  - Sahs, Adolph L., 1938-1959 (Box 155, Folder 2102)
  - Salter, William T., 1921-1953 (Box 155, Folder 2103)
  - Sanborn, Walter, 1927-1931 (Box 155, Folder 2104)
  - Sanders, F. Kingsley, 1923-1948 (Box 155, Folder 2105)
  - Sanders, Morris B., 1930-1955 (Box 155, Folder 2106)
  - Sapristein, Milton R., 1938-1960 (Box 155, Folder 2107)
  - Sarton, George, 1928-1951 (Box 155, Folder 2108)
    See also: boxes 79-96, folders 1116-1145
  - Sarton, May, 1954-1959 (Box 155, Folder 2109)
  - Saugman, Per, 1954-1958 (Box 155, Folder 2110)
  - Saunders, J. B. de C. M., 1943-1959 (Box 155, Folder 2111)
  - Saunders, W. B. Co.
    See: box 175, folders 2614-2615
  - Sayers, Ross V., 1951-1959 (Box 155, Folder 2112)
  - Scammon, Richard E., 1933-1941 (Box 155, Folder 2113)
  - Scarff, John E., 1934-1957 (Box 155, Folder 2114)
  - Schaltenbrand, Georges, 1926-1956 (Box 155, Folder 2115)
  - Schaltenbrand, Hans H., 1937 (Box 155, Folder 2116)
  - Scher, Allen Myron, 1948-1958 (Box 155, Folder 2117)
  - Schick, William, 1931-1935 (Box 155, Folder 2118)
  - Schiller, Joseph, 1958-1959 (Box 155, Folder 2119)
  - Schmerl, Ernst, 1948-1949 (Box 155, Folder 2220)
  - School of Aviation Medicine: Randolph Field, 1941-1944 (Box 156, Folder 2221)
  - Schoolcraft, John, 1939-1941 (Box 156, Folder 2222)
  - Schoonmaker and Co., 1937-1940 (Box 156, Folder 2223)
  - Schorr, Marvin G., 1946-1954 (Box 156, Folder 2224)
  - Schramm, Elizabeth E., 1934-1955 (Box 156, Folder 2225)
  - Schreiber, Carl F., 1931-1935 (Box 156, Folder 2226)
  - Schroeder, Charles, 1933-1941 (Box 156, Folder 2227)
  - Schullian, Dorothy, 1945-1960 (Box 156, Folder 2228-2230)
    See also: box 195-197, folders 1-30
  - Schulman, Arnold A., 1953-1956 (Box 156, Folder 2231)
  - Schultz, Adolph, 1931-1950 (Box 156, Folder 2232)
  - Schuman, Henry
    See also: box 38, folder 555
    - 1934-1943 (Box 156, Folder 2233-2235)
    - 1944-1960 (Box 157, Folder 2236-2247)
  - Schusdek, Alexander, 1948 (Box 158, Folder 2248)
  - Schwartz, Henry G., 1937-1939 (Box 158, Folder 2249)
  - Schwartz, Neena, 1947 (Box 158, Folder 2250)
  - Schwartz, R. Plato, 1939-1941 (Box 158, Folder 2251)
  - Schweitzer, Alfred, 1938 (Box 158, Folder 2252)
  - Science, 1928-1945, 1952 (Box 158, Folder 2253)
  - Science Service, Inc., 1928-1935, 1944, 1957 (Box 158, Folder 2254)
  - Scientia, 1930-1937 (Box 158, Folder 2255)
  - Scientific Monthly, 1931-1939, 1957 (Box 158, Folder 2256)
  - Scott, Thomas F. McNair, 1928-1936 (Box 158, Folder 2257)
  - Scoville, William B., 1948-1952 (Box 158, Folder 2258)
  - Searle and Co., 1949-1950 (Box 158, Folder 2259)
  - Second World Conference on Medical Education, 1959 (Box 158, Folder 2260)
  - Selling, Lowell S., 1932-1939 (Box 158, Folder 2261)
  - Semans, James, 1956-1957 (Box 158, Folder 2262)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1932-1950
    See: box 187, folder 2887
  - Share, Leonard, 1947-1960 (Box 158, Folder 2263)
  - Sharpey-Schafer, Edward
  - Shastid, Thomas Hall, 1932-1946 (Box 158, Folder 2264)
  - Shaw, Ralph R., 1946 (Box 158, Folder 2265)
  - Sheehan, Donal
    - 1933-1937 (Box 158, Folder 2266-2267)
    - 1938-1958 (Box 159, Folder 2268-2269)
  - Shenkin, Henry A., 1941-1959 (Box 159, Folder 2270)
  - Sherburn, George, 1949-1950 (Box 159, Folder 2271)
  - Sherrington, Carr and Margarete, 1925-1960 (Box 159, Folder 2272)
  - Sherrington, Charles Scott
  - Shields, Randolph T., 1935-1941 (Box 159, Folder 2273)
  - Shryock, Richard H. (Box 159, Folder 2274)
    See also: series II, boxes 240-246, folders 706-766
    See also: box 79-96, folders 1116-1145
  - Sigma Xi
    - General, 1932-1945 (Box 159, Folder 2275)
    - Chapters
      - Beloit, 1940 (Box 159, Folder 2276)
      - Mayo Clinic, 1939-1940 (Box 159, Folder 2277)
      - Stanford, 1939-1940 (Box 159, Folder 2278)
      - State College of Washington, 1939-1940 (Box 159, Folder 2279)
      - Swarthmore, 1939-1940 (Box 159, Folder 2280)
      - University of Illinois, 1940 (Box 159, Folder 2281)
      - University of Vermont, 1940 (Box 159, Folder 2282)
      - University of Washington, 1939-1940 (Box 159, Folder 2283)
      - Yale University, 1932-1944, 1951 (Box 159, Folder 2284)
  - Sikand, Rajinder S., 1949-1959 (Box 159, Folder 2285)
  - Silvette, Herbert, 1935-1955 (Box 160, Folder 2286)
  - Simmons, James S., 1942-1944 (Box 160, Folder 2287)
  - Simonart, André, 1931 (Box 160, Folder 2288)
  - Simpson, Levy, 1929-1932 (Box 160, Folder 2289)
  - Sinclair, Hugh M., 1934-1960 (Box 160, Folder 2290)
  - Singer, Charles, 1932-1959 (Box 160, Folder 2291-2292)
  - Singh, Inderjit, 1949-1959 (Box 160, Folder 2293)
  - Sinnot, Edmund W., 1946-1952 (Box 160, Folder 2294)
  - Sizer, Theodore, 1932-1959 (Box 160, Folder 2295)
  - Sjöqvist, Carl Olof, 1938-1954 (Box 160, Folder 2296-2297)
  - Smith, Charles E., 1942-1944 (Box 161, Folder 2298)
  - Smith, Elizabeth R. B., 1932-1939 (Box 161, Folder 2299)
  - Smith, G. Elliot, 1930 (Box 161, Folder 2300)
  - Smith, Homer W., 1933-1957 (Box 161, Folder 2301)
  - Smith, Lucia Wheaton, 1921 (Box 161, Folder 2302)
  - Smith, Paul K., 1939-1950 (Box 161, Folder 2303)
  - Smith, Thomas M., 1956 (Box 161, Folder 2304)
  - Smith, Wilbur, 1931-1938 (Box 161, Folder 2305)
  - Smithsonian Institute, 1928-1932, 1952-1955 (Box 161, Folder 2306)
  - Snider, R. S., 1941 (Box 161, Folder 2307)
  - Societé Italiana di Storia delle Scienze, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 2308)
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1926-1955 (Box 161, Folder 2309)
  - Society of Apothecaries of London, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 2310)
  - Society of British Neurological Surgeons, 1948-1960 (Box 161, Folder 2311)
  - Society of the Alumni of Presbyterian Hospital (New York City), 1940 (Box 161, Folder 2312)
  - Sollman, Torald, 1939 (Box 161, Folder 2313)
  - Somberg, Harold M., 1945-1954 (Box 161, Folder 2314)
  - Soriano, Victor, 1945-1960 (Box 161, Folder 2315)
  - Sosman, Merrill C., 1928-1958 (Box 161, Folder 2316)
  - Southworth, Hamilton, 1943-1945 (Box 161, Folder 2317)
  - Spector, Benjamin, 1941-1960 (Box 162, Folder 2318)
  - Speer, Christopher S., 1950 (Box 162, Folder 2319)
  - Spencer, Susan B., 1939 (Box 162, Folder 2320)
  - Spiegel, Ernest, 1929-1954 (Box 162, Folder 2321)
  - Spies, John W., 1929-1958 (Box 162, Folder 2322)